=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 16=
=الخاطبة الحمراء الصغيرة= =الحلقة 16=
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I've set them up.
لقد قمت بإعدادهم.
I should be happy.
يجب أن أكون سعيدا.
Well,
حسنًا،
have I fallen for him?
هل وقعت في حبه؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Love is unpredictable.
الحب لا يمكن التنبؤ به.
What's impossible about it?
ما هو المستحيل في ذلك؟
Yue Lao, are you doing some tricks?
يو لاو، هل تقوم ببعض الحيل؟
Cheers.
هتافات.
Why did you break up a loving couple
لماذا انفصلت عن زوجين محبين
and seize my chance?
وأغتنم فرصتي؟
How should I know about your love
كيف يجب أن أعرف عن حبك
with Miss Muke?
مع الآنسة موك؟
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's not all your fault.
ليس كل خطأك.
It's because I've repeatedly failed.
هذا لأنني فشلت مرارا وتكرارا.
I'm not worthy of Muke.
أنا لا أستحق موك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Muke.
نحن.
What would you like to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
The West Lake vinegar fish is good.
أسماك الخل في البحيرة الغربية جيدة.
Do you want to try it?
هل تريد أن تجربه؟
All right.
حسنًا.
West Lake vinegar fish.
أسماك الخل في البحيرة الغربية.
Our marriage?
زواجنا؟
Well…
حسنًا…
I'll follow your decision.
سأتبع قرارك.
Then…
ثم…
Oh.
أوه.
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
Yes.
نعم.
You must be hungry.
لابد أنكم جوعى.
Give it a try.
جربها.
Right.
يمين.
Indeed, I am no match for Dr. Jiang.
في الواقع، أنا لست ندًا للدكتور جيانغ.
He's talented and wealthy.
إنه موهوب وثري.
Compared to him,
مقارنة به،
all I have is a sincere heart.
كل ما لدي هو قلب صادق.
I'm sentimental.
أنا عاطفي.
It's not about love.
الأمر لا يتعلق بالحب.
As life comes to an end,
ومع اقتراب الحياة من نهايتها،
my bitterness is endless.
مرارتي لا نهاية لها.
I love.
أنا أحب.
I hate.
انا اكره.
I don't deserve it.
أنا لا أستحق ذلك.
Since I met you,
منذ أن التقيت بك،
I've never fallen for other men.
لم أقع أبدًا في حب رجال آخرين.
In my whole life,
في حياتي كلها،
I've always
لقد كنت دائما
only loved you.
أحببتك فقط.
Take me with you.
خذني معك.
Okay.
تمام.
What are you laughing at?
على ماذا تضحك؟
Sit.
يجلس.
Oh.
أوه.
West Lake vinegar fish.
أسماك الخل في البحيرة الغربية.
Five,
خمسة،
four,
أربعة,
three,
ثلاثة،
two.
اثنين.
How does it taste?
كيف طعمها؟
It's sour.
إنه حامض.
Is it just sour?
هل هو حامض فقط؟
Hmm.
همم.
It's sweet too.
انها حلوة جدا.
Will my father come after me?
هل سيأتي والدي بعدي؟
No.
لا.
My Master is stalling him.
سيدي يعطله.
Hurry up, Zhang Sheng is waiting.
أسرع، تشانغ شنغ ينتظر.
Ghosts.
أشباح.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Don't stop me. Let me die.
لا توقفني.  دعني أموت.
I don't want to live anymore.
لا أريد أن أعيش بعد الآن.
Stop her.
قف هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
So,
لذا،
you eloped with someone and were sold to a brothel.
لقد هربت مع شخص ما وتم بيعك إلى بيت للدعارة.
That's why you attempted suicide.
ولهذا السبب حاولت الانتحار.
I sponsored him
لقد قمت برعايته
to take the imperial examination,
لإجراء الامتحان الإمبراطوري،
waiting for him to succeed.
في انتظار نجاحه.
To climb the social ladder,
لتسلق السلم الاجتماعي،
he sold me to a brothel.
لقد باعني إلى بيت للدعارة.
I was so stupid,
لقد كنت غبيًا جدًا،
not listening to my parents' advice.
عدم الاستماع إلى نصيحة والدي.
Now,
الآن،
I'm afraid of going back to face my parents.
أنا خائف من العودة لمواجهة والدي.
I can only end it all with death.
لا أستطيع أن أنهي كل هذا إلا بالموت.
When will the faithless man arrive?
متى سيصل الرجل غير المؤمن؟
I hope
آمل
I have never met him.
لم يسبق لي أن التقيت به.
Why is there a faint scent of fox?
لماذا هناك رائحة باهتة من الثعلب؟
Some men are unfaithful,
بعض الرجال غير مخلصين
while women are loyal to love.
بينما المرأة مخلصة للحب.
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Yes?
نعم؟
Will Zhang Sheng treat me this way too?
هل سيعاملني Zhang Sheng بهذه الطريقة أيضًا؟
Muke.
نحن.
Zhang Sheng would never do that to you.
تشانغ شنغ لن يفعل ذلك لك أبدًا.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
he can't succeed.
لا يستطيع أن ينجح.
Huh?
هاه؟
Muke.
نحن.
If you believe he can make you happy,
إذا كنت تؤمن أنه يستطيع أن يجعلك سعيدًا،
don't look back and move on.
لا تنظر إلى الوراء والمضي قدما.
Hmm.
همم.
Okay.
تمام.
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
I believe in Zhang Sheng.
أنا أؤمن بـ تشانغ شنغ.
Be happy.
كن سعيدا.
Okay.
تمام.
Who is that heartless man you mentioned?
من هو ذلك الرجل القاسي الذي ذكرته؟
I must avenge you.
يجب أن أنتقم لك.
It's in the past.
إنه في الماضي.
Just let it go.
دعها فحسب.
But I can't.
لكن لا أستطيع.
You fox demon.
أيها الثعلب الشيطاني.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
remember to wash off the fox stench from your body.
تذكر أن تغسل رائحة الثعلب الكريهة من جسمك.
(To be continued)
(يتبع)
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
I have a lot to tell you.
لدي الكثير لأخبرك به
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل عميق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪